I can't stop.
I love you.
I love you
I miss you
No matter what words I choose
I wonder if they'll reach you
I don't know.
Cut.
Here's the cut.
I'll just shoot as fast as I can.
Go, go, go, go!
You're shooting from a very close angle, aren't you?
Both sides of the camera
A little bit of a jokey look.
Cute!
I love the way the lens moves on this camera.
I love the way the lens moves. It makes me go "wow!
Like, "Oh my gosh, it just moved!" Like, "Oh my gosh, it just moved!
I love it!
It moves so much!
I love the way it opens and closes like eyes, like pupils.
I love looking into people's eyes.
Even if it's just for a second.
Just open them a little bit more.
That's so cute!
They say people fall in love when they look into each other's eyes for 7 seconds.
If I like a guy that much, I can look him in the eye for three seconds.
Is this going to work for me?
Yes, yes, yes.
Amazing.
If we do this, if we look at each other for 7 seconds, can we fall in love?
I could fall in love.
You're so cute.
We're going to perform now.
Okay, we're cutting.
Okay, thank you very much.
Yes, thank you very much.
You seem confident.
Confident.
Please give me an expression.
Cute.
This is the MC's conversation.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Very nice.
It's so cute.
So beautiful.
Thank you.
It's OK.
Yay!
Thank you.
I got it.
Here's your cut.
Here you go, cut.
Thank you very much.
Amazing.
I'll let you choose.
Palma took the picture.
Thank you very much.
The last one with the biggest smile.
Bon appétit!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work
Yes, I did the one sol cut.
I was nervous
Cool.
I'm turning
Here's the cut.
With the voice.
"When people look at each other for seven seconds...
"I'm going to fall in love with you.
And I'm like, "I can do this.
Like this.
Ichi does that sometimes.
Like this junior high school kid.
I got a hand.
I'm pretty sure this is what they use, right, Love One?
Really.
Position 3, because it's nice to go down like that, like it looks delicious.
That's what everyone's noticing.
Yay!
Now all we have to do is capture it, guys.
Okay, let's do a little test one time.
Go, go, go, go, go!
I'm eating this now!
What are you guys doing?
It's good, isn't it? This...
What did you eat? And...
You're wearing a camera!
He's wearing a camera!
Not even that one.
Here we go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
You're done.
You're done!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Yes, cut.
Yes, OK.
We're done.
I did my best.
We did our best.
Well, let's do a real tronda, Zalma.
Yay!
Who wants to do it?
I want to play oni.
First, goo, then rock-paper-scissors.
Who loses?
I want to play oni.
First, goo, then rock-paper-scissors.
Yes, Iichigo 2.
Zalma-san is tronda.
Dharma-san fell down!
Dharma fell down!
Touché!
Ready, ready!
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one,
Bunkei is the verbal expression of the being zeroed in on.
Just a hand signaled the end of the game.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much. There is a lot going on. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I'm playing playing playing.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
From the shooting of the drama to the music video shooting today, thank you for your help day after day.
We are
One Love One Heart
It was One Love One Heart
Thank you very much.
I'll take some pictures.
Okay.
Here we go.
A few.
Here you go.
Love one pose
Yes, sir
Cute!Cute.
Three more to go.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Oh, sorry. We're done.
A little cartoon. Sorry, sorry, excuse me. It all happened so fast.
I'm looking forward to seeing how it turns out.
I hope it will be a song that can support everyone's voice!
Bye bye!